Welcome to the Hugging Face Course! This  course has been designed to teach you all   about the Hugging Face ecosystem: how to  use the dataset and model hub as well as   all our open source libraries. Here is  the Table of Contents. As you can see,   it's divided in three sections which become  progressively more advanced. At this stage,   the first two sections have been released. The  first will teach you the basics of how to use   a Transformer model, fine-tune it on your own  dataset and share the result with the community.   The second will dive deeper into our libraries  and teach you how to tackle any NLP task. We are   actively working on the last one and hope to  have it ready for you for the spring of 2022.   The first chapter requires no technical knowledge  and is a good introduction to learn what   Transformers models can do and how they could be  of use to you or your company. The next chapters   require a good knowledge of Python and some basic  knowledge of Machine Learning and Deep Learning.   If you don't know what a training and validation  set is or what gradient descent means,   you should look at an introductory course such as  the ones published by deeplearning.ai or fast.ai.   It's also best if you have some basics in one  Deep Learning Framework (PyTorch or TensorFlow).   Each part of the material introduced in this  course has a version in both those frameworks,   so you will be able to pick the one you are  most comfortable with. This is the team that   developed this course. I'll now let each of  the speakers introduce themselves briefly.